# Karel Verschraegen

https://www.linkedin.com/in/karel-verschraegen/ https://github.com/karelverschraegen/ https://karelverschraegen.com/ karelverschraegenbiz@gmail.com Ghent, Belgium

Full stack software engineer with 4+ years of experience delivering high-quality software in TypeScript, React and NestJS. Proven success in rapid prototyping, product development, leadership, technical problem-solving, coordination and communication.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AIKIDO Ghent

Full Stack Software Engineer

February 2023 - May 2023

- Help discover product-market-fit with newly built features by rapidly prototyping and iterating based on collected feedback
- Improve onboarding experience, licence scanning...

CHEQROOM
Tech lead

July 2022 - February 2023

- Manage and host scrum meetings (stand-ups, sprint reviews...)
- Communicate and coordinate feature releases and bug fixes
- Unblock team members, provide feedback and technical insights
- Tackle technical debt, large refactors and general maintenance

AIKIDO Ghent

Full Stack Software Engineer

July 2019 - July 2022

- Set up a communication layer between Knockout and React
- Build out design system and accompanying component library
- Set up and deploy GraphQL microservices on AWS
- Automate the deployment process via GitHub Actions

RIALTO Ghent Intern February 2019 - May 2019

- Learn React, Redux and TypeScript
- Build a floor plan drawing tool based on SVG's

# **Education**

## **COLLEGE UNIVERSITY GHENT**

Ghent

Bachelor of Applied Computer Science

2016 - 2019

Honours: Cum Laude

#### Additional skills

- Communication and coordination
- Leadership
- Problem solver
- Independent
- Curious